(Howard:)Bernadette, please, I'm asking you
to give me another chance.
(Bernadette:)What do you think, Leonard?
Should I give him another chance?
(Leonard:)It's up to you.
He didn't call your experiment stupid.
Come here, tushy-face.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Tushy-face.
That is going on Twitter right now.
(Bernadette:)Raj, you should've seen
Leonard's experiment.
The interference pattern was cool
when the electron beam was on.
(Leonard:)I'm glad you enjoyed it. Most people
aren't that interested in what I do.
[CLEARS THROAT]
(Penny:)Actually, that's not true, Leonard.
(Penny:)I've been thinking that, given
the parameters of your experiment...
(Penny:)...the transport of electrons
through the nano-fabricated rings...
...is no different than the experiment
already conducted in the Netherlands.
(Penny:)Their observed phase shift in
the diffusing electrons inside the ring...
...already demonstrated
the electric analogue...
(Leonard:)...of the Aharonov-Bohm
quantum interference effect.
(Penny:)That's it. That's all I know.
(Penny:)Oh, wait.
(Penny:)Fig Newtons were named after a town
in Massachusetts, not the scientist.